Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
M_I_SForEver
Hurricane Vera
currently a Category Four storm
and strengthening.
A lot of damage is expected,
especially from the winds...
...is announcing that the trial
against Los Urabenos drug cartel
has been postponed
due to the weather...
The case against
the Colombian drug cartel
may be Hurricane Vera's
first casualty.
Courts, city officials,
all being sent home...
Please follow
emergency evacuation
instructions.
If unable to shelter in...
Moving fast and expected to be
through the D.C. Metropolitan
area in the next hour.
Don't be fooled by clear sky...
Hurricane Vera,
currently a Category Four storm
and strengthening.
Catastrophic wind damage
is expected.
Mandatory evacuations
have been in effect
but that window
is already closing
as the storm
is about to make landfall
and the outer bands
are already here
reminding so many
of Hurricane Sandy
a few years back.
The D.C. and Virginia area
directly in the crosshairs.
Let's tie this bird down.
They're shutting down
the airport.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Rapido, rapido, rapido.
Everybody in.
A very
dangerous situation right now.
If you look behind me
you can see
what we're seeing now
streets practically empty.
Everyone who was supposed
to evacuate has done so
for the most part.
We're looking
at a strong Category Four
at landfall, so...
Can we go over this?
A very
dangerous situation right now.
I just wanna make sure
we have the correct info
for your testimony.
OK.
Your work with the cartels
started five years ago?
Six.
So, our sources tell us that
they recently moved their money
into a cryptocurrency.
Do you know anything about that?
And the flight?
They landed. They're fine.
They got in
just before the storm.
They should be here soon.
They're all I have.
Amelia and her father.
You understand?
I need to know
that they will be safe.
I will testify...
but I want it in the papers.
Promise me
that we will be protected
here in the US
not in Colombia.
We can't go back there.
It's not safe.
You don't know what
they've done to my family there.
Promise me.
Yes.
It's in the witness
protection agreement.
You have nothing to worry about.
I promise you.
Not too far now.
A few more miles,
we'll be at the safe house.
OK, got 'em.
Heading south on Mission.
OK?
- You guys alright?
- Everybody alright in the back?
- Uh-huh.
- I'm good.
I'm hit.
How bad?
Don't worry about me.
Protect the package.
Give me your hand.
Stay down!
Go!
Get low! Stay low!
Get in, get in, get in!
Calm. Stay calm.
What are you looking for?
I thought we hit them.
They're around here somewhere.
They're not here.
Let's get out of here, man!
Agent Armstrong, you copy?
This is Agent Bennett.
Do you copy?
This is Armstrong.
What's your status,
Agent Bennett?
We have the girl and her dad.
We've commandeered
an.
Headed to...
to rendezvous point Nakatomi.
West on Hamel.
ETA ten minutes.
You stay here, if they come!
Where are you going?
Evacuation
orders have gone out...
Yes, no, I know it's a lot
of money I'm asking for
but you know I'm good for it.
Come on, Don
you've been servicing our loan
since my dad...
Yes.
Yes, no, I know my credit rating
is not great right now
but you know it was the divorce
that caused that.
Let me ask you one thing.
Would you even consi...
Hello?
Linda!
Taylor, where have you been?
They're freaking out.
Who turned the fire alarm on?
Who do you think?
Fire alarms are not
for fire emergencies only.
They can be used
in case of any emergency
to notify the proper...
OK. OK, Arthur, we got it.
Thank you.
Any word on the county van?
Can't reach 'em.
You're kidding.
They're supposed to check
on our pick-up an hour ago.
- Phones are down.
- Ugh! Crap!
They're late. Where are they?
We've got to get
everyone out of here.
Can you try the landline?
- I tried it. It's out too.
- The landline?
Well, not because of the storm.
I can't believe they shut us off
in an emergency.
It's a freaking hurricane.
I take it the call with Don
didn't go well?
I think this is finally it.
Come on, don't give up so easy.
You promised him.
Well, my dad
was a big dreamer, OK?
I'm a realist.
I can't save everybody.
You know,
I did everything I could.
This is it, Linda.
Where is everyone?
I'm here!
Rose?
Ida?
Any... Anything on the vans yet?
Lines are still dead.
What are we gonna do?
Again, Hurricane Vera, currently
a Category Four storm and...
Oh, is Fonzy cooking again?
I'm not gonna just stand here
and listen to this guy.
Who do you think you are,
bossing us around?
He's a colonel.
Lieutenant Colonel.
Yeah, right.
"Colonel", with air quotes.
See? Air quotes.
Hey. Hey.
What's going on in here?
- And why is the food out, Fonzy?
- I'm hungry.
You're a stress eater.
Yeah, and don't think
we don't know
you've been cooking
in your room.
Yeah. So?
You have anger issues, too.
Yeah, but...
I'm working on it.
You gotta tell this guy, T
we got a van coming
to pick us up.
He says we have to stay here
and shelter.
Yeah, shelter in place.
And it's not me, it's the news.
It's too dangerous
to go out there anyway.
Look, if you have
a problem with it
you can take it up
with the authorities.
You want us to stay here
and get blown to smithereens?
You tell him, T.
Well, the truth is, everyone
I'm not sure
the evacuation van's coming.
Oh, good Lord.
Hold on!
Hold on, everyone. Hold on.
Are you sure that's what you
heard about shelter in place?
Yeah, Sheriff Rightmire
held a press conference
said everyone in the county
who hasn't already evacuated
is to shelter in place.
We're not to leave.
Is that what everyone heard?
I heard it.
I heard it, too.
OK. Alright.
- Well, shelter in place it is.
- Oh.
Let's get everyone back
to their rooms for now, OK?
Mm. She don't look good to me.
Tired.
I'll get the candles out
in case the power goes out.
It'll be romantic. Eh, Rosie?
You keep your candles
to yourself.
Mm.
Stay down.
Let me take a look at that.
You need to put pressure
on that. Hold tight.
We gotta leave. Let's go.
Keep low. Keep low.
Uh... Back to your room, please.
Oh, come on, T.
Thank you.
All of you, just for now,
please...
Ooh!
Wiggle it.
There's a trick to it.
Oh, I always forget that.
OK.
How do you always
stay so calm in all of this?
I've been through
a few storms before.
It'll be alright.
Alright...
If the power goes out,
the monitor has a backup battery
and that'll...
That'll kick in, OK?
So, just leave that on.
How did I live 93 years
without that thing?
That's not what's keeping
my heart going, honey.
Yeah, well...
I know it's hard times
here right now.
Don't worry about your life,
what you will eat or drink.
Look at the birds of the air.
They neither sow nor reap
and yet,
your heavenly Father feeds them.
Don't worry.
He'll provide.
I wish I could believe that.
You will. Just like your father.
Do you want me
to help you get back into bed?
No. I'm fine.
No. No, thanks.
Ladies...
No. Go sit down.
Oh, let me help you with that.
Sorry.
They wanted to be together.
It's hard to say no.
Although, technically,
Taylor's right.
FEMA recommends
staying in interior rooms
in situations like this.
Whatever, nerd.
I'm just saying, don't blame me
if we all get buried in debris.
Oh, Arthur!
Just take them all.
Put us all out of our misery.
Oh, no. Today's Tuesday only.
You do not want to combine
Tuesday and Wednesday, trust me.
Mixing days equals purple haze.
Alright.
Alright, kids, that's enough.
We can stay in here. Alright?
Just for now though.
- How's she doing?
- We're hanging in there.
DEA.
Can we come in, please?
Need help.
Come on in, sweetie.
Cole Bennett, DEA.
Hi, I'm Taylor Ward.
I'm the owner of this place.
What happened? Is he hurt?
Is this is a medical facility?
- Assisted living.
- What's going on?
Linda, can you please
grab them some towels?
- Do you have a doctor here?
- I'm a nurse. No doctor, no.
- What happened?
- We've been in a collision.
These people
are under my protection
as possible witnesses
in a federal trial.
There's a FEMA command post
about eight blocks away.
The phones are dead.
I've gotta make it
there on foot.
Can I leave them in your care?
- Ma'am?
- Yeah. Of course, yes. Yes.
Taylor, what's going on?
Can you prep room 203, please?
We'll put them up there.
You'll be OK.
Like I said, we're
assisted living. I'm not...
I'm not sure I can help
but I'll do whatever I can.
Appreciate it.
You'll be alright here.
Take care of your father.
Thank you.
Just come right in here.
There we go.
Alright...
Let's take a...
I need to take a look if
I'm gonna be able to help you.
What happened?
Que paso?
Hablar Inglés?
Yes.
What's your name?
He is Francisco.
I am Amelia.
Taylor.
Let me take a look.
OK.
...we have debris
flying everywhere.
We have a hubcap.
I would definitely recommend...
This is a bullet wound.
I'm not equipped
to take this out here, OK?
I'm gonna dress it
as best as I can
until I can get you
to a hospital.
- Did you get through with 911?
- No, the storm, it's...
I need gauze and supplies.
We're out of gauze.
You're kidding me.
Alright, here,
put some pressure on that.
Let's go take a look, alright?
Come on.
He went up the road.
From your mama.
Take it.
Keep it...
always.
No...
Little sparrow.
Don't worry. It will be alright.
Keep it.
Es muy importante.
Prometeme.
Promise me.
I promise. I will.
OK, let's see what
we can do here, huh?
OK.
We are followed.
Being followed? By who?
Men.
Bad men.
Sicarios.
OK, let me take a look at this.
He's bleeding out.
He's bleeding out. Linda!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Shh.
It's OK. Amelia, help me
calm him down, sweetheart.
It's OK. It's OK.
It's OK.
What was that?
I hope that wasn't a branch
going through a window.
Linda!
That was no branch.
Amelia, I want you
to do me a favour here.
Give me your hands.
I want you to put a lot
of pressure on there, OK?
More than you think you should.
I'm gonna be back
as soon as I can.
OK, lock this door behind me
and then put the pressure
back on, OK?
Papa.
Stay right there.
- OK.
- You in charge here?
Yes.
There a man
and a little girl here?
A man and a little girl here?
Huh?
Told you we hit them.
- I'm gonna ask you...
- No!
One last time.
Is there a man...
...and a little girl here?
You have two seconds!
OK! Please! Please!
OK. OK, come with me.
Walk.
- Walk!
- OK! OK!
Hey!
- Hurry up.
- OK.
- Move.
Faster.
Hey, hey...
Hey, hey, look.
I want the man
and the girl, not you.
It's OK.
- OK.
- Walk.
Hey, hey, hey!
What's in here?
- It's just a guest room.
- Shh!
Are they armed?
I don't know.
Where are they?
- I don't know.
- Were they in there?
- Were they...
- Yes, they were. Yes.
Shh.
Stay with me. Come on.
What's in there?
Nothing.
It's just a laundry room.
Knock on the door and tell them
it's you. Tell them to open up.
Hello, it's me.
Can you open the door?
Move away!
Ay, pobrecito.
You don't look good, Paisa.
Let's do this quick.
Where's the code?
Is it on a chip or something?
Flash drive? Something?
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Wake up.
Where is it?
Hey, hey, hey!
Look. Look at me. Look!
Is it... Is it in here? Huh?
Hey, hey. Dígame.
Tell me, where is it?
Or I'll do to you
what I did to your brother.
Dígame. Dígame, eh?
You think you could
turn your back on us, huh?
You think these Americans
are gonna protect you
more than me?
Hey, hey.
Hey, look, look, look...
I don't care
if your wife testifies.
I don't care.
That's my uncle's business. Hmm?
He sent us here to take you out,
but forget him.
He's not as considerate as I am.
Look, look, look, look...
You give me the code,
we split it.
We do our own thing. Hmm?
I'll give you
as much as you want.
You, your family, you walk.
Hey, you give me that code
and we're rich.
We're very rich, my man.
Hey, hey...
I just need that code.
You... You have it?
You... Your daughter has it?
Think you can turn
your back on me?
Hey, hey, hey!
Please, stop.
Please.
He needs medical attention.
What do you know?
I don't know anything, I swear.
- They gave it to you?
- They didn't give me anything.
I swear.
Hey, hey, hey!
Where's the money?
Tell me, where's the money?
Where's the money, huh?
Where's the money?
Hey! Hey!
Hey, hey.
Hey, wh... where's the money?
Hey, where's the money?
Where's the girl?
I don't... I don't know.
- Wait! Wait.
- What?
Wait. You want a flash drive
or something, right?
If it's that,
I... I have a place...
- Walk. Walk!
- OK.
OK...
What's this?
Um...
Plug it in. Plug it in.
Step away.
What?
I'm hungry.
Uh, business hasn't been
so great lately.
Yeah?
You think you have it bad here
in this big fancy mansion?
It's not what it looks like.
I inherited this place
from my father.
You have no idea.
Your dad religious?
He started this place
as a church ministry
as a way to...
give back to people that...
had spent their lives
helping other people.
Yeah, he was.
So was I...
then things happened.
You ever invest
in cryptocurrency?
You should.
See...
I'm in a family business, too.
You do what you gotta do.
So do I.
Where is that?
These are old.
We don't even use them...
Enough with the games already!
Take me there now. Walk!
Move.
Move!
Amelia, run!
Hey, no gun. No gun!
Chachita...
Chachita?
Psst.
They're not going anywhere
not with this storm.
Let's just wait.
What are you doing?
- Como?
- What are you doing?
This place got about 100 rooms.
You wanna go through 'em all?
The girl.
Guzman sent us to end this.
Shh.
Don't worry about my uncle.
We're doing it my way.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
OK.
They'll come to us.
About time you guys
invited us girls to your club.
We'll make an exception today.
Is everyone OK?
Mmm...
Poor Linda.
I just can't believe it.
Poor, poor Linda.
She ain't never done
nothing wrong to nobody.
Nobody!
W-we can't
just stay down here.
We need to come up with a plan.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah?
Who made you
captain of the ship?
I'm sorry
but where are we gonna go, huh?
We can't just
leave Taylor alone up there.
T-that's what I'm saying.
You gonna lead us into battle,
Mr Fake Colonel?
Will you leave him alone?
What is your problem?
He acts like he's the boss
when he's no different
than the rest of us.
Isn't that right?
Tell 'em... "Colonel"!
What is wrong with you?
This is hardly the time to...
No, he's right.
He's right. I'm not a colonel,
if you must know.
I was in the Army...
but when my battalion
shipped out, I couldn't go.
Turned out
I had a spinal condition.
Unfit to serve, they said.
So, I spent the whole
Korean affair
in an office behind a desk.
Never fired a shot.
Though, I did rise up
through the ranks.
It was easy, when all the men...
all the real men were gone.
I was a major.
I was set for promotion
to lieutenant colonel
and then my battalion came back,
most of them.
And they said
"Fraser... you're gonna be
a lieutenant colonel?"
We had a good laugh about it
and they saluted and laughed.
So, when it came time
for the promotion...
I denied it.
Just said, "never mind."
So, you're right...
I'm not a colonel
not even a lieutenant colonel.
I don't know any more or
have any special qualifications
to get us out of this mess
than anyone else here.
So...
There it is.
Oh, who cares?
My husband spent the Korean War
making a fortune
sneaking beer provisions
and then selling them
on the side.
Listen, ain't none of us heroes.
What we gonna do now
is what I wanna know.
Ida?
- I...
- Hold my hand.
That's it. Come on.
Come on.
Oh, Heavenly Father...
we come to you now.
We need you.
Yes, Lord.
Is this gonna be
one of her long ones?
Please watch over the girl...
the little girl, Father.
- Keep her safe.
- Mm-hmm.
Protect her from this evil.
Keep her safe...
under the shadow of your wing.
Thank you, Lord.
And we lift up Taylor
to you now, Lord.
Yes.
We pray
that she turns to you now.
Her burden is heavy
but your burden is light.
And keep us all safe
in this storm.
We know that trials happen...
but You are greater.
Help us all
to trust in You entirely.
In Your name, we pray.
Honour His name.
Oh, sweetie, it's just me.
It's OK. I'm not gonna hurt you.
You can trust me.
It's OK. It's OK.
It's OK. Shh.
Shh. It's OK.
It's OK.
It's OK. It's OK.
These men,
they're looking for something.
Some kind of code or something.
Do you know what it is?
No.
If we find it and give it
to them, they'll go away.
Are you sure?
I don't know.
OK.
We've gotta get outta here.
If I can get you
out of this house
do you think you can run
to one of the nearby neighbours
and get us help somehow?
OK, it's not safe.
We better find somewhere safe
for you. Let's go. Come on.
Alright...
On my signal... we run.
Three... two... one.
He goes down, we go up.
You live here?
You're rich.
It just looks like that.
Trust me.
This way.
Come on.
Oh, wow.
Right here.
Right through here.
You must have a big family.
It sure feels like it sometimes.
Where are they?
Oh, don't worry about them.
They're pretty resourceful.
They'll be around here
somewhere.
Come on. Right through here.
Right this way, sweetie.
OK.
Alright, don't judge.
It's OK. My room's messy, too.
OK.
Wow.
I haven't been in here
in a long time.
You did this?
Not recently, but...
yeah, when I was about your age.
Well, I almost forgot.
What is that?
Well, it's...
a place where I keep important
things for safekeeping.
Who is that?
- That's me.
- That's you?
That's my mum and dad
when they were still with us.
This was taken on the day
they opened this place.
They wanted to open
a place for poor people
so that when they got older,
they had a place to live.
Who are all those people?
These were people
from the church.
People that donated
their time and...
and their money
so that we could open.
I remember this day.
They were all in the entrance
of the church
and they were saying
this really long prayer and...
all I could think about was,
"When are we gonna eat?"
Look at those smiles.
I haven't seen that in a while.
Amelia, I have to go
and check on...
What is this?
That was my favourite shell
that my best friend gave me.
Do you have
a brother or a sister?
Do you?
Not anymore.
I had a sister... a big sister.
I'm sorry.
It's OK.
I hardly remember.
I was little.
It was the cartel.
Do you have kids?
No.
Oh.
I wanted to, but I couldn't.
Sorry.
It wasn't meant to be, I guess.
Sometimes we just have to trust
God has a different plan.
I need to go downstairs.
I need to check on my friends
and make sure they're OK.
OK.
I want you to stay here, though.
You'll be safe here.
OK.
I will.
What does that mean?
Get rid of them.
Taylor?
Hello?
Hey! Come here!
Come here! Come here! Come here!
Come on. Come on!
Enough!
We do it my way.
We wait.
So...
No one knows anything, huh?
You have something
that belongs to me.
You give it to me and we...
we go.
Look, I told you, we don't know
what you're looking for.
OK? We don't have
anything to do with this.
No!
Sit down! You will tell me.
Tell me where it is!
I don't know.
I don't know what it is.
The code from your papa.
Where is it? Where is it?
That's enough.
You have to know! You tell me!
No se! No se, por favor!
That's enough!
None of us.
Listen to me.
I wanna talk to you.
Tu y tu muchachos.
Mira, mira!
You have done enough here.
You have done enough!
You and your men
will leave this place
and never come back again.
This is a good place...
a safe place.
You don't know this,
so I am going to tell you.
When her father opened this home
he dedicated it with a verse
a Bible verse, Isaiah 25:4.
"A refuge for the needy
in their distress...
a shelter from the storm..."
A shelter from the storm!
That is perfect!
Especially for today.
Do you know
what else Isaiah 25 said?
"In that day they will rise up
and they will say
'Surely He is our God.
We trusted in Him...
and He saved us.'"
He saved us!
So, you...
can threaten us...
you can hurt us
but you cannot destroy us...
because we are safe.
Not in this house...
we are safe in Him.
He is our fortress.
And now, get out!
You're not safe!
How dare you?
Who do you think you are?
She's a 93-year-old woman.
Ninety-three years old
and she has more courage
in her little finger
than you will ever have.
You are a coward!
A coward.
Shut up.
Go! Go!
Move!
Help me with this.
Push!
Push! Push!
Stay down!
No...
What are you doing?
You're gonna get us killed!
It's all clear in there.
Everybody OK?
Is she alright?
No, she needs help.
I'll be right back.
- Any other bad guys?
- You alright?
No, just the three.
Where's your dad?
Donde tu papa?
I'm sorry.
Are you gonna be OK?
You sure?
I have to ask you something.
Where's the code...
that your dad had with him?
You don't know?
I know it's difficult
right now, OK?
But I need you
to think real hard for me.
I don't know.
You sure you don't know
where it is?
It's very important.
OK.
No problem.
Listen up, everyone.
If I can just get your attention
for a minute.
I'm Cole Bennett with the DEA.
There's an important
piece of evidence
this young lady
and her father were transporting
as part of an investigation.
Without it...
some very bad men will go free.
What is it?
What does it look like?
Not exactly sure.
It's a code on a computer drive,
a chip of some kind.
Have any of you seen
anything like that?
- No.
Are you sure?
We're sure.
Can I ask you again?
I want you to think, honey.
Think back when you first
got here with your dad.
I don't know.
I cannot remember.
Come on.
Think!
What's going on?
Let me guess...
You're looking for a code.
Do you know where it is?
I don't know anything
about your business.
None of us do.
One of you... does.
What are you doing?
Listen to me.
Tell me where the code is.
Where is it?
Your father had a bag...
a black bag.
Where is it? Speak up!
Where is it?
Ah...
All of a sudden,
you know things.
Let her go.
All of you stay here.
Do you understand?
Stay here!
Understood.
Oh, my God.
Are you OK?
Miss Taylor?
Come on.
Alright, stay with me.
The girl... she's OK?
That's OK. It's OK.
Hang in there.
Hang in there. I got you.
- I got...
- Listen.
Trust...
Him.
No...
No, no!
I...
I can't! Oh...
I can't, I can't. Oh!
I can't do this anymore.
I can't do this any...
Miss Taylor.
- Hey.
- I can't... I...
Come on now.
Snap out of it.
It's gonna be OK.
Ida would say that.
That's right.
One step at a time.
That's what she'd say.
Trust the next step.
Hey...
You hear that?
Hmm?
Exactly.
Me neither.
Must be the eye of the storm.
You know...
I think I like that look.
Where you going?
I'm gonna take
that next step.
This way?
Come on, let's keep looking.
No!
Come on, Amelia! Go! Go!
Alright, let me think.
Hide. Hide here. Hide here.
OK...
What do you think
you're doing, huh?
You know where it is.
You want to keep
that money for yourself.
It's mine.
You know how many years
I put into this?
Filthy barrio slums.
Filthy slum rats...
bringing drugs in here.
Whose side are you on?
They're killing my men.
Our men.
That traitor...
and his daughter
are in the middle of it.
So was her mother.
And I will get rid
of that little runt, too...
if she doesn't tell me
what I wanna know.
Come here.
I'm so sorry.
- I'm so sorry...
- It's T! It's T!
It's OK.
OK.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Amelia, do you know
what these papers are?
A little bit.
Miss Ward is applying
for foster care.
Do you know what that is?
I think so.
It means that, if you want to...
you may be able
to stay here for a while.
I can stay with her?
Well, there are a few things
to go over, but...
we might be able
to make that happen.
Oh, just a sec.
I think I know
where she might be going.
We'll be right back.
OK.
What's that?
My father gave it to me.
He said it belonged
to my mother.
It's very pretty.
He told me
not to let anyone have it
so I hid it here, like you did.
Can I see it for a second?
Your father was right.
This is a very,
very special necklace.
Someone I was very close to
once told me
that all you have to do
is trust.
An abuelita?
Yeah.
That even when you think
something's impossible
there is always, always a way.
My father was right
about this place.
It's very special.
Like my necklace?
Yeah...
like your necklace.
This is a very valuable gift.
Make sure you cherish it always.
Ooh, what is this?
Oh, wow, I haven't seen that
in a long time.
Do you like to draw?
- Yeah.
- Me too.
At home I had
a bunch of pictures in my room.
You did?
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull